Privacy Policy
==============

#### Last Updated: August 14, 2025

_This Policy takes effect on 14 August 2025 for new users. It takes effect for existing users on 15 September 2025._

_You may find the previous version of our Privacy Policy [here](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy-deprecated)._

By using Bluesky, you acknowledge that you have read and understand the information in this Policy.

### Table of Contents

1. [Introduction](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#introduction)
2. [What is Personal Data?](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#personal-data)
3. [Informing us of changes](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#informing-changes)
4. [Applicability of this Policy](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#applicability)
5. [Third-party Services](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#third-party-services)
6. [If you do not want to provide Personal Data](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#no-personal-data)
7. [Updates to this Policy](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#updates)
8. [Personal Data We Collect](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#data-collection)
9. [Cookies](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#cookies)
10. [How We Use Personal Data](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#data-use)
11. [How We Share your Personal Data](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#data-sharing)
12. [International data transfers](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#international-transfers)
13. [Your Privacy Choices and Rights](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#privacy-rights)
14. [Retention of Personal Data](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#data-retention)
15. [Supplemental Notice for Certain Jurisdictions](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#jurisdictions)
16. [Security](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#security)
17. [Children's Personal Information](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#children)
18. [Contact Us](https://bsky.social/about/support/privacy-policy#contact)

* * *

1\. Introduction
----------------

Bluesky Social, PBC ("**we**", "**us**", "**our**") respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting any of your Personal Data we process. Bluesky owns and operates a microblogging mobile application ( "**Bluesky App**" or "**the App**") and desktop application (available at bsky.app and bsky.social; each a **"Site"**; the App and Sites, collectively, **"Bluesky"**) that run on the Authenticated Transfer Protocol ("**AT Protocol**"). Your use of Bluesky is subject to this privacy Policy ("**Policy**") as well as the [Bluesky Terms of Service](https://bsky.social/about/support/tos), [Community Guidelines](https://bsky.social/about/support/community-guidelines), and [Copyright Policy](https://bsky.social/about/support/copyright). The AT Protocol Network Services Privacy Policy is found [here](https://bsky.social/about/support/network-services-privacy-policy).

This Policy explains what we do with our users’ Personal Data. It also explains how we handle Personal Data in the context of our relationships with other businesses.

We process your Personal Data when you use Bluesky and to provide the services that we offer via Bluesky (the "**Services**"). We are a "data controller" of the Personal Data that we process in connection with the Services. This means that we decide why and how we process Personal Data about you.

If you have any questions about this Policy or our processing of your Personal Data, please see Section 18, Contact Us, for contact information.

We may update this Privacy Notice from time to time. We will post these changes on the Site or in the App. We may also send you other notifications about these updates.

2\. What is Personal Data?
--------------------------

"**Personal Data**" is information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular person or household.

We may also collect data that is not associated or linked with your or that cannot be used to identify you, like deidentified, aggregated or anonymised information. This is not Personal Data and is not subject to this Policy.

3\. Informing us of changes
---------------------------

Please keep us informed if your Personal Data changes at any point during your relationship with us so we can keep our records accurate and current. Update your Personal Data in the App or on the Site.

4\. Applicability of this Policy
--------------------------------

This Policy is separate from our [Terms of Service](https://bsky.social/about/support/tos) and our [Community Guidelines](https://bsky.social/about/support/community-guidelines), that also govern your use of Bluesky.

5\. Third-party Services
------------------------

Bluesky and the Services may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins, applications, services, products, and technology (“**Third-party Services**”). Clicking on links to and using Third-party Services may allow third parties to collect or share your Personal Data. We are not responsible for the content, security or privacy practices of those Third-party Services and this Policy does not apply to your use of Third-party Services. You should consider the privacy and cookie policies / notices of those third parties to find out how your Personal Data may be used.

6\. If you do not want to provide Personal Data
-----------------------------------------------

We need to collect certain Personal Data to give you access to Bluesky or to specific features and functionalities of Bluesky, in accordance with our agreements with you. Applicable laws also require us to process certain Personal Data about you. If you do not want to provide Personal Data we request, we may not be able to provide you with access to the Bluesky app or to specific features and functions of Bluesky.

7\. Updates to this Policy
--------------------------

We may update this Policy from time to time, and any updates will be effective when we post the revised Policy on Bluesky. We will use reasonable efforts to notify you of any material updates to this Policy, by sending you a message in the App or on the Site, or at the email address you provide to us.

You should review this Privacy Notice every time you access a Bluesky App Service.

8\. Personal Data We Collect
----------------------------

We process, or our third-party providers may process for us, different kinds of Personal Data:

1. **Personal Data you provide**
    1. **Account Creation.** We collect information like email address, phone number, images you associate with your profile, birth date and username when you create a Bluesky account.
    2. **Your Communications with Us.** We may collect personal information, like your name, email address, or phone number when you contact us.
    3. **Your Posts.** The Bluesky App is a microblogging service that lets you post content and comment on other users' posts. We collect your posts. Your posts and comments are public, so exercise care when deciding what to share.
    4. **Your Direct Messages.** We store and process your direct messages so you can communicate directly with other users on the Bluesky App. These are unencrypted and can be accessed for Trust & Safety purposes.
    5. **Job Applications.** If you apply to work with us, we collect any personal information you provide with your application.
    6. **Payment Information.** When you make a purchase, a third party service provider that handles payments for us will receive the payment information you provide, including your payment card information.
    7. **Account Recovery.** If you lose control of your account for some reason and need to recover it, we may ask you to provide information that helps us confirm your identity.
2. **Personal Data We Collect Automatically**
    1. **Usage Information.** When you use Bluesky, we collect certain information automatically, including your Internet protocol (IP) address (which can be used to derive your general location), user settings, cookie identifiers, mobile carrier, other unique identifiers, browser or device information, and Internet service provider (ISP). We may also collect personal information about your use of Bluesky, including the posts you view on Bluesky, the links you click within Bluesky, and the frequency and duration of your activities.
    2. **Cookies (and Other Technologies).** We and third parties that provide content or other functionality on Bluesky may use cookies, pixel tags, and other technologies (**"Tracking Technologies"**) to automatically collect information. See Section 9, Cookies, for more information.
3. **Personal Data We Collect from Other Sources**
    1. **Third Parties, generally.** We may collect personal information from third parties. For example, you may direct a developer application or other third-party social networking application to share personal information with us or you may live in a jurisdiction that requires age verification and we will collect information from a third-party provider telling us whether you meet certain age requirements.
    2. **Third Party Age or Identity Verification.** Where required by law, Bluesky may use third-party services to verify that you are old enough to access certain features or content. This verification may involve one or more of the following methods, depending on your jurisdiction and availability:
        1. **Government ID Verification:** Uploading an image of a government-issued ID, which is checked for authenticity.
        2. **Facial Age Estimation:** Uploading a selfie or real-time facial scan used to estimate age via machine learning technology.
        3. **Payment Card Verification:** Providing a valid payment card to confirm age through a nominal transaction or validation check.
        4. **Knowledge-Based Verification (KBV):** Answering questions based on public records to confirm identity and age.
        5. **Social Vouching:** A verified adult vouches for the user's age using their own verified account or identity.
        6. **Mobile Phone Verification:** Using a phone number linked to a mobile carrier account to infer your age.
        7. **Email Based Age Inference:** Using publicly available data about an existing email account to infer your age.You will be able to choose from among available jurisdiction-specific options based on your preference. We do not retain any biometric data or facial images provided to third-party age verification vendors.

9\. Cookies
-----------

We use cookies and other Tracking Technologies to collect certain information automatically. Tracking Technologies allow a website to recognize your device and can serve several purposes: to ensure that the website takes the user’s preferences into account by storing language preferences, to collect statistical data and adapt the content. Tracking Technologies can help provide you with a good experience when you browse websites and also help improve website functionality.

1. **Strictly Necessary Cookies.** Some cookies are strictly necessary to make our Bluesky App Services available to you. We cannot provide you with our Bluesky App Services without this type of cookie.
2. **Analytical or Performance Cookies.** We may also use cookies for website analytics purposes in order to operate, maintain and improve our Bluesky App Services. We may use our own analytics cookies or use third-party analytics providers.

You can block cookies by setting your internet browser to block some or all cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including strictly necessary cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the Sites and the Bluesky App. You can change your browser settings to block or notify you when you receive a cookie, delete cookies or browse our Sites using your browser’s anonymous usage setting.

Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about how to adjust or modify your browser settings. If you do not agree to our use of cookies or similar Tracking Technologies which store information on your device, you should change your browser settings accordingly. Where required by applicable law, you will be asked to consent to certain cookies and similar Tracking Technologies before we use or install them on your computer or other device.

10\. How We Use Personal Data
-----------------------------

We will only use your Personal Data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose.

The list below indicates the purposes for which we collect and process your Personal Data. Some of the above grounds for processing will overlap and there may be several grounds which justify the processing of a single category of Personal Data.

1. **To Provide Our Services.** We use personal information to fulfill our contract with you and provide Bluesky and the Services, such as:
    1. Managing your account;
    2. Providing access to certain areas, functionalities, and features of the Bluesky App Services;
    3. Answering support requests; and
    4. Communicating with you about your account, activities on the Bluesky App Services, and policy changes.
2. **For Administrative Purposes.** We use personal information for various administrative purposes, such as:
    1. Pursuing our legitimate interests like direct marketing, research and development (including marketing research), network and information security, and fraud prevention;
    2. Detecting security incidents, protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity, and taking appropriate actions against malicious actors;
    3. Measuring interest in, and engagement with Bluesky and with Services;
    4. Creating de-identified and/or aggregated information;
    5. Carrying out analytics;
    6. Improving, upgrading, or enhancing Bluesky and Services;
    7. Developing new products and services;
    8. Ensuring internal quality control and safety;
    9. Sharing information with third parties as needed to provide Bluesky and Services;
    10. Enforcing our agreements and policies; and
    11. Carrying out activities that are required to comply with our legal obligations.
3. **For Marketing.** We may use personal information to provide you with marketing. If you have any questions about our marketing practices, you may contact us using the information provided below. You can opt-out from receiving marketing communications from us by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each e-mail.
4. **With Your Consent.** We may use personal information for other purposes that are clearly disclosed to you at the time you provide personal information or with your consent.
5. **Other Purposes.** We also use your personal information for other purposes as requested by you, as permitted by applicable law, or where we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose.
6. **Legal Bases for Processing.** For explanations of our legal bases for processing in jurisdictions where this disclosure is required, see Section 15, Supplemental Notice for Certain Jurisdictions, below.

11\. How We Share your Personal Data
------------------------------------

1. **Sharing to Provide Bluesky and Services**
    1. **Your Posts and Public Profile.** Bluesky is a decentralized microblogging service where most user activity is public by design. This includes your posts, profile, likes, following, and blocks.
    2. **Other Users You Share or Interact With.** Bluesky may allow you to share personal information, messages, or interact with other users.
    3. **Third-party Services You Share or Interact With.** Bluesky may link to or allow you to interface, interact, share information with, direct us to share information with, access and/or use Third-party Services. If you do, the information you share will be subject to any Third-Party Service's privacy policy. For example, if you request that we share your personal information with a developer application or payment processor, we may facilitate the request.
    4. **Service Providers.** We may share Personal Data with our third-party service providers and vendors. This includes service providers and vendors that provide us with IT support, hosting, payment processing, customer service, and related services.
    5. **Business Partners.** We may share Personal Data with our business partners to provide you with a product or service you have requested. We may also share your personal information with business partners with whom we jointly offer products or services.
2. **Sharing to Protect Us or Others.** We may access, preserve, and disclose any information we store if we, in good faith, believe doing so is required or appropriate to: (i) comply with law enforcement, regulatory, or national security requests and legal process, like a court order or subpoena; (ii) protect your, our, or others' rights, property, or safety; (iii) enforce our policies or contracts; (iv) collect amounts owed to us; or (v) assist with an investigation or prosecution of suspected or actual illegal activity.
3. **Sharing with other Bluesky Companies.** We may share with parent or subsidiary companies to coordinate and manage our business, in accordance with the purposes set out in this Policy. These recipients will process Personal Data in the same way as set out in this Policy.
4. **Sharing to obtain Professional Services.** We may share Personal Data with our legal advisors, bankers, auditors, accountants, consultants, and insurers. Our professional advisors will process Personal Data as necessary to provide their services to us.
5. **Sharing in the Event of Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers.** If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, purchase or sale of assets, transition of service to another provider, or other similar corporate transaction, your personal information may be processed as part of such a transaction.

12\. International data transfers
---------------------------------

We may transfer, process, and store all personal information we collect anywhere in the world. Different countries have different data protection laws.

If we transfer personal information from the European Economic Area, Switzerland, Brazil and/or the United Kingdom to a country that does not provide an adequate level of protection under applicable data protection laws, we will do so (i) using appropriate safeguards; (ii) based on safeguards like the European Commission-approved, UK Government-approved, or Brazil’s Data Protection Authority Standard Contractual Clauses or Addenda; or (iii) otherwise in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If we transfer personal information from the European Economic Area, Switzerland, Brazil and/or the United Kingdom to a country that does not provide an adequate level of protection under applicable data protection laws, we will do so (i) using appropriate safeguards; (ii) based on safeguards like the European Commission-approved, UK Government-approved, or Brazil’s Data Protection Authority Standard Contractual Clauses or Addenda; or (iii) otherwise in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

For more information about the safeguards we use for international transfers of your personal information, please contact us as set forth below.

13\. Your Privacy Choices and Rights
------------------------------------

1. **Your Privacy Choices.** The privacy choices you have about your Personal Data information are determined by applicable law and are described below.
    1. **Email Communications.** If you receive a marketing email from us, you may opt out by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of such email. You will continue to receive transaction-related, non-promotional emails related to Bluesky. You will not be opted out of those communications.
    2. **Mobile Devices.** We may send you push notifications through our App when you enable them. You may opt out from receiving these push notifications by changing the settings on your mobile device. We may collect precise location-based information via the App, but only if you permit us to do so. You may opt out of this collection by changing the settings on your mobile device.
    3. **"Do Not Track".** Do Not Track (**"DNT"**) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. Please note that we currently do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers, as there is no consistent industry standard for compliance.
2. **Your Privacy Rights.** Depending on what laws apply to your Personal Data, you may have the right to:
    1. **Request Access to and Portability of Your Personal Information,** including: (i) obtaining access to or a copy of your personal information; and (ii) receiving an electronic copy of personal information that you have provided to us, or asking us to send that information to another company in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format (also known as the "right of data portability");
    2. **Request Correction** of your personal information where it is inaccurate, incomplete, or outdated. We may provide self-service tools for you to update your personal information;
    3. **Request Deletion, Anonymization or Blocking** of personal information including when processing is based on your consent, or when processing is unnecessary, excessive or noncompliant (also known as the "right to be forgotten").
    4. **Request to Opt-Out of Certain Processing Activities** if we engage in certain data processing activities that give you a right of opt-out under applicable privacy laws;
    5. **Request Restriction of or Object to** our processing of your personal information;
    6. **Withdraw your Consent** to our processing of your personal information. Please note that your withdrawal will only take effect for future processing and will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal;
    7. **Be Informed** about third parties with which your personal information has been shared; and
    8. **Request the Review of Decisions Taken Exclusively Based on Automated Processing** if these decisions could affect your rights under applicable data protection laws.

Please contact us using the information in Section 18, Contact Us, if you would like to exercise any of these rights. We will process your requests in accordance with applicable laws. Before fulfilling your request, we may ask you to provide information to verify your identity. There are exceptions and limitations to each of these rights, and while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases instantly or within a reasonable period of time, we may retain information for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so. Some laws may allow you to appeal our decision if we decline to process your request.

We abide by relevant response timelines where those timelines apply. In the UK, EU, and Brazil, our policy is to resolve simple requests within 30 days and complex requests within 60 days. Our policy also recognizes the 45 day response timeline in certain US states.

If your personal information is subject to the applicable data protection laws of Brazil, the European Economic Area, Switzerland, or the United Kingdom, and you believe our processing of your personal information violates applicable law, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent supervisory authority.

* [Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC)](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home/the-fdpic/contact.html)

14\. Retention of Personal Data
-------------------------------

We keep the Personal Data we collect for as long as you use the Bluesky App Services, or as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which we collected it. There are also other reasons why we may keep personal information. They may include, but are not limited to, providing Bluesky and Services, resolving disputes, establishing legal defenses, conducting audits, pursuing legitimate business purposes, enforcing our agreements, for trust and safety purposes, and complying with applicable laws.

When determining the retention period, we make case-by-case determinations, taking into account various criteria, like the type of products and services requested by or provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, the impact on Bluesky and the Services we provide to you if we delete some personal information from or about you, mandatory retention periods provided by law, and any relevant statute of limitations.

We generally retain Personal Data as follows:

* **Providing our Services.** Where we need Personal Data to provide Services, or specific parts of our Services, we will retain your Personal Data for the lifetime of your account or as long as necessary to provide such Services (or parts thereof).
* **Trust and safety.** If we reasonably suspect you have violated our [Terms of Service](https://bsky.social/about/support/tos), or where we otherwise need to retain information to identify and report illegal activity or protect our users and third parties, we will retain relevant Personal Data for as long as necessary to conduct our investigations, assist with any governmental or non-governmental investigations, and to enforce any removal of offending users or content.
* **Compliance with applicable laws and regulatory and contractual obligations.** For example: (i) identity record keeping / maintenance requirements in certain locations and financial / tax reporting requirements; (ii) if we receive a valid legal request (like a preservation request or search warrant, related to your Personal Data); (iii) complying with regulatory investigations or proceedings. We will delete your Personal Data sooner where a shorter retention period is required by applicable law.
* **Legal claims.** Personal Data will be retained in accordance with applicable statutory limitation periods. In certain circumstances we may need to retain this longer, for example, to defend ourselves in litigation.

15\. Supplemental Notice for Certain Jurisdictions
--------------------------------------------------

1. **U.S. States**
    
    Where required by law, these U.S. State Privacy Disclosures ("**U.S. Disclosures**") supplement the information contained in the Policy by providing additional information about our Personal Data processing practices relating to individual residents of certain U.S. States. Except where otherwise stated, defined terms in this Policy retain the same meaning in these U.S. Disclosures.
    
    In these U.S. Disclosures, Personal Data does not include publicly available information or deidentified, aggregated or anonymised information that is maintained in a form that is not capable of being associated with or linked to you.
    
    1. **No Targeted Advertising Sales.** We do not sell or share Personal Data for the purpose of displaying advertisements that are selected based on Personal Data from your activities on or use of Bluesky ("**Targeted Advertising**").
    2. **Sensitive information.** We may disclose sensitive information for a business purpose like those described below, we do not sell or share sensitive information for the purpose of Targeted Advertising.
        
        The following Personal Data elements we, or our service providers, collect may be classified as "sensitive" under certain privacy laws ("**Sensitive Information**") including:
        
        1. username and password;
        2. birthday;
        3. telephone number;
        4. government identifiers (like driver's license numbers);
        5. payment information; and
        6. confirmation that a user is 18 years old or older.
        
        We use this sensitive information for the purposes described in Section 10, How We Use Personal Data, to the extent necessary to operate Bluesky and our Services, to enter into and perform on a contract with you, to comply with legal and regulatory requirements, to protect the safety of our users and third parties, or as otherwise permissible for our own internal purposes consistent with applicable laws.
        
    3. **Deidentified information.** We may receive or process Personal Data to create deidentified information that can no longer reasonably be used to infer information about, or otherwise be linked to, a particular individual or household. Where we maintain deidentified information, we will maintain and use it in deidentified form and will not try to reidentify the information except as required or permitted by applicable law.
    4. **Appeals.** If you are a resident of certain U.S. States, you have the right to appeal decisions regarding your privacy requests. All appeal requests should be submitted using the contact details found in Section 18, Contact Us. If your appeal is denied, you may contact your local Attorney General.
    5. **CALIFORNIA SPECIFIC DISCLOSURES** The following disclosures only apply to California residents:
        
        1. **Personal Data collection.** California law requires that we provide disclosures to you about what Personal Data we collect by reference to the categories of Personal Data set forth within California law. To address this obligation, we have identified the relevant California Personal Data category for the Personal Data set out in Section 8, Personal Data we Collect:
            
            1. **Identifiers** like your name, address, phone number, email address, passport or other government identity information including driver's licence information, account information, or other similar identifiers.
            2. **Customer Records** like your driver's licence number, passport number, partial debit card information, partial credit card information, bank account information or other payment or financial information.
            3. **Protected Classification Characteristics** like age, date of birth, and gender.
            4. **Commercial Information** like information about products or services purchased and your use of our Services.
            5. **Biometric Information** which is described above and which is collected only by third-party providers to the extent necessary to conduct age or identity verification. We do not collect, receive, possess, or have access to this data.
            6. **Internet / Network Information** like device information, and log data.
            7. **Sensory Information** like pictures and videos (content) you upload.
            8. **Professional / Employment Information** like the business or organisation you are associated with and, where applicable, your title with that business or organisation and information relating to your role with the business or organisation.
            9. **Other Personal Data** like communication preferences, customer service and communication history, personal data an individual permits us to see when interacting with us through social media, Personal Data an individual provides us in relation to a question or request, and messages you send us through our Services or make available to us on social media.
            10. **Inferences** like information generated from your use of our Services.
            
            We may disclose all of these categories of Personal Data for a business purpose to service providers or other third parties, as outlined in this Policy.
            
        2. **Disclosure of Personal Data.** As detailed in Section 11, How We Share your Personal Data, we may disclose the categories of Personal Data identified above to the following categories of third parties for various business purposes: other Bluesky companies, service providers, our professional advisers, business partners, other businesses as needed to provide our Services, and certain third parties where you have provided consent, where it is in connection with a corporate transaction, or where we are required by law or in connection with other legal process.
        3. **Sources of Personal Data.** We collect Personal Data from you, from your browser or device when you interact with our Services, from our business partners and affiliates, from third parties you direct to share information with us, and from other third-party providers. For more information, see Section 13, Your Privacy Choices and Rights.
        4. **Purpose for collection.** We collect Personal Data about you for the purposes described in Section 10, How We Use Personal Data.
        5. **Notice of financial incentives.** We do not sell Personal Data collected about you, or share Personal Data collected about you for cross-context behavioural advertising. We do not currently send emails for direct marketing purposes.
        
        You may exercise your rights in relation to your Personal Data as outlined in this Policy, and as applicable, by submitting a ticket through your account or by emailing [support@bsky.app](mailto:support@bsky.app).
        
    6. **NEVADA SPECIFIC DISCLOSURES**
        
        Nevada law requires operators of online services to provide a way for Nevada residents to request to opt-out of the sale of Personal Data. Although we do not sell Personal Data, Nevada residents can still submit this type of opt-out request by contacting us using the details listed in Section 18, Contact Us.
        
    7. **EU and UK GDPR**
        
        This Supplemental Notice for EU/UK GDPR only applies to our processing of personal information that is subject to the EU or UK GDPR. Personal information means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. If you do not provide your personal information when requested, you may not be able to use our Bluesky App Services if that personal information is necessary to provide you with our Bluesky App Services or if we are legally required to collect it.
        
        We process personal information when we have a valid legal basis, including as set forth below:
        
        1. **Performance of a Contract:** Bluesky may need to process your personal information where required to perform our contract with you, namely the Terms of Service, and for the purposes described in Section 4(A) of this Privacy Notice.
        2. **Legitimate Interest:** Bluesky may process your personal information where we or a third party have a legitimate interest, including the purposes in Section 4(B) of this Privacy Notice. We only rely on our or a third party's legitimate interest to process your personal information where these interests are not overridden by your interests or fundamental rights and freedoms.
        3. **Consent:** In some cases, Bluesky may also rely on your consent to process your personal information.
        4. **Compliance with our Legal Obligations:** Bluesky may process your personal information to comply with our legal obligations. For example, we may process your personal information to comply with tax, labor, and accounting obligations.
        
        **Data Protection Officer:** Bluesky has appointed a Data Protection Officer (DPO). You may contact our DPO at Ametros Group Ltd, Lakeside Offices, Thorn Business Park, Rotherwas Industrial Estate, Hereford, Herefordshire, HR2 6JT, [dpo@ametrosgroup.com](mailto:dpo@ametrosgroup.com).
        
        **Data Protection Representative:** Bluesky has appointed a Data Protection Representative (DPR) for both the UK and EU. You may contact Bluesky's EU Representative at Ametros Ltd, Unit 3D, North Point House, North Point Business Park, New Mallow Road, Cork, Ireland, gdpr@ametrosgroup.com. You may contact Bluesky's UK Representative at Ametros Group Ltd, Lakeside Offices, Thorn Business Park, Rotherwas Industrial Estate, Hereford, Herefordshire, England, HR2 6JT, [gdpr@ametrosgroup.com](mailto:gdpr@ametrosgroup.com).
        
    8. **Brazil LGPD**
        
        This Supplemental Notice for Brazil's General Data Protection Law (Law No. 13.709/2018 – the "**LGPD**") only applies to our processing of personal data that is subject to the LGPD. For purposes of the LGPD, personal information means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual.
        
        If you are a user of Bluesky App Services in Brazil, the below additional terms: (a) are incorporated into this Privacy Notice; (b) apply to your use of the Bluesky App Services, and (c) supersede and control over any conflicts in the rest of the Privacy Notice to the extent of any inconsistency.
        
        1. **Legal bases.** We guarantee that the processing of personal information subject to the LGPD by us will be always carried out in accordance with one of the legal bases that include: (1) your consent; (2) compliance with legal or regulatory obligations; (3) execution of a contract with you; (4) to exercise our rights in contracts or judicial, administrative or arbitral proceedings; (5) the protection of your – or third parties' – life and physical safety; (6) our legitimate interests; (7) credit protection; (8) prevention of fraud and the safety of the data subject in processes of identification and authentication.
        2. **Data Subject's Rights.** In addition to the rights outlined in section 7 of this Privacy Notice, for purposes of the LGPD you also have the right to:
            1. **Obtain confirmation that we process your personal information.** In response to this request, we will inform you whether we process your personal information or not. Please note that, if you are a user, we necessarily process your personal information.
            2. **Obtain information about the possibility of not providing your consent and the respective consequences.** When consent is used as a legal basis for the processing of your personal information, you have the right to be informed about the possibility of not providing consent and the consequences of refusal.

16\. Security
-------------

We make reasonable efforts to protect your information by using physical and electronic safeguards designed to improve the security of the information we maintain. However, as our Services are hosted electronically, we can make no guarantees as to the security or privacy of your information.

17\. Children's Personal Information
------------------------------------

The Bluesky App Services are not directed to children under 13 (or other age as required by local law outside of the United States). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children.

If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child has uploaded personal information to our site without your consent, you may contact us using the information provided below.

18\. Contact Us
---------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@bsky.app](mailto:support@bsky.app).
